So ever since I stopped arguing with people who make nonsense comments on my posts and just block
them, it has really honestly restored my nervous system. But I still be wanting to share you with
you all some of the nonsense that I see. And here is an example. I did a post where I talked about
the reason why they're redacting these files is not merely about protecting Trump, but more so
about protecting Israel. And this man said, no, it's just that simple. It's about protecting Trump
and that's it. And I was like, well, I don't know who you are to just like shut it down, but it's not
that simple. His response is where is the Israel evidence in those files? I'm not even going to
read anything else because this is the arrogant confidence that people show up with. This man
said, where is the Israel evidence in the Epstein files? Yeah. And he's a lawyer said that with his
whole chest, this is why you have to really learn and read and understand for yourself because people
like him will come with arrogant ignorance. Now, since it's Kreml, I feel like we should all just
be giving. I'm actually going to unblock him so that he can read the comments that you all are welcome
to put in the thread right here, right below, explaining to him where Israel is in the Epstein
files. Happy Yuletide. As that deceased podcaster's wife would say, Merry Christmas and Shabbat Shalom.
I think you'll find, sir, that there will come a time when Black people wake up and become
intellectually independent enough to think for themselves. As other humans are intellectually
independent enough to think for themselves, then the Black man will think like a Black man
and he will feel for other Black people. And this new thinking and feeling will cause Black
people to stick together.